futuregenerali.in 2014-12-27

# Welcome to Future Generali India | Life Insurance | General Insurance

We are committed to protecting Your privacy and have taken reasonable steps to protect the confidentiality of the Personal Information You have furnished to us and its transmission through the world wide web.

In the process of You using this Website or availing of the existing or future services or Facility provided by the Website, You may be required to furnish information, personal or otherwise, relating to you, including information that is of a confidential nature (all such information being part of “Personal Information” as defined herein). You are urged to keep the Personal Information current so as to ensure that the services and Facility remain relevant and reach You.

Future Generali India undertakes not to disclose, except as otherwise provided, the Personal Information provided by You to any person, unless such action is necessary to:

  * Conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process;
  * Protect and defend Future Generali India’s or its Affiliates' rights, interests or property;
  * Enforce the terms and conditions of the products or services or Terms and Conditions; or
  * Act to protect the interests of Future Generali India, its Affiliates, or its members, constituents or of other persons.

You shall not disclose to any person, in any manner whatsoever, any information relating to Future Generali India or its Affiliates of a confidential nature obtained in the course of availing the Facility or use of Website. Failure to comply with this obligation shall be deemed a serious breach of the terms herein and shall entitle Future Generali India or its Affiliates to terminate the services or Facility, without prejudice to any damages, to which You may be entitled to or can access otherwise.

We may, and are authorised to, share the Personal Information with a third party, including Affiliates, that is interested in serving You. You may inform us at any time not to share Your Personal Information with third parties by sending us an e-mail message at care@futuregenerali.in. We may also use Your Personal Information for the purposes of providing You with any services to which You subscribe, and any service-related activities such as collecting subscription fees from You for those services, and notifying You or contacting You regarding any problem with, or the expiration of, such services. In this regard, it may be necessary to disclose Your Personal Information to one or more Advisors and contractors of Future Generali India and their sub-contractors, but such Advisors, contractors, and sub-contractors will be required to agree to use the information obtained from us only for these purposes.

We may, and are  authorised to, share part with all Personal Information related to the details and transaction history of the Customers to its Affiliates / banks / financial institutions / credit bureaus / agencies / participation in any telecommunication or electronic clearing network as may be required by law, customary practice, credit reporting, statistical analysis and credit scoring, verification or risk management and You shall not hold Future Generali India liable for use or disclosure of Personal Information.

We will also use the Personal Information for the following purposes:

  * Allow You to access specific account information;
  * Providing customization. We may use the Personal Information provided by You to customize Your visit to the Website by displaying appropriate content at our judgment and discretion;
  * Send you information about us and / or our products and services;
  * To contact you when required.
  * Future Generali India’s Affiliates may from time to time send by e-mail or otherwise, information relating to their products and services.
  * Please be aware that other websites that have links to our Website may collect personally identifiable information about you. This privacy statement does not cover the information practices / privacy policy of those websites or advertisers.

top
